(Leonard:)Oh, hi.
(Penny:)Hey, you.
(Penny:)What happened with
the contacts?
(Leonard:)One of them's upstairs.
(Leonard:)The other one sort of slipped
back into my skull.
(Penny:)Hey, is that one of the new
shirts Priya got you?
(Priya:)Yeah.
(Penny:)You don't wanna
wash that.
(Leonard:)No?
No, that's silk.
(Penny:)Seriously, what would you do
without me?
Yeah. (chuckles)
(Penny:)You know, I gotta
tell you, I think
(Penny:)you got a real winner
with Priya.
Yeah, me, too.
(Penny:)She seems really sweet.
(Penny:)Believe me, you do not want
to take that for granted.
(Penny:)There are a lot of bitches
out there.
(Leonard:)Yeah, bitches are the worst.
All right, I'll
see you later.
(Leonard:)Uh, Penny, there's something
I have to tell you.
(Penny:)What?
(Leonard:)Okay, uh, how do I put this?
(Leonard:)Um... are you familiar with
Darwin's observation
(Leonard:)of the finches
in the Galapagos Islands?
(Penny:)Did they make a movie about it?
(Priya:)No.
(Penny:)Then no.